youpoll.me 2017-05-03

# Privacy policy

Privacy policy
Last modified: May 18, 2016
Creative Pages LLC (collectively "we", "us", or "our") created this privacy policy to inform you of our
commitment to protecting your personal information while visiting youpoll.me. As you use youpoll.me, we
want you to understand how we use information and the ways you can protect your privacy. Your privacy
matters to us, so whether you are new to youpoll.me or a long-time user, please take the time to get to
know our policies.
What information do we collect from you?
We collect information to provide better services to our users. We collect information in the following
ways:
    Information you give us. For example, you have the option to sign up for a user account to easily
     access and manage your polls from a personal user page. When you sign up you have the option
     to provide your email address. Email addresses are only used if you need to reset your password.
    Information we get from your use of our services. We may collect information as you use
     youpoll.me in the following ways:
      o     Cookies
            A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the
            user. We use cookies to collect and store information when you visit youpoll.me and this
            may include sending one or more cookies to your device. For example, a cookie may be
            used to uniquely identify your browser or your user account. Usage of a cookie is in no way
            linked to any personally identifiable information while on youpoll.me. We do not and will not
            use cookies to collect personal information from any user.
      o     IP Address
            An Internet Protocol address is a series of alphanumeric characters separated by periods or
            colons that identifies each computer or device on a network. IP addresses are only stored to
            prevent vote tampering on youpoll.me. Usage of an IP address is in no way linked to any
            personally identifiable information while on youpoll.me. We do not and will not use IP
            addresses to collect personal information from any user.
      o     Google Analytics
            Google Analytics is a simple, easy-to-use tool that helps us measure how users interact with
            youpoll.me. As a user navigates between web pages, Google Analytics records information
            about the page a user has seen, for example the URL of the page. Google Analytics uses
            cookies to "remember" what a user has done on previous pages of the website. We use this
            information, such as page views and bounce rate, to help us make your experience at
            youpoll.me better. However, it is important to remember that Google Analytics
            does not collect any personal information from youpoll.me users.
We will never ask you for any sensitive information, including but not limited to credit card or social
security numbers. Do not give out any of your sensitive information to anyone claiming to be from
youpoll.me or Creative Pages LLC.
How do we use the information we collect?
We use information collected from cookies to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our
services. For example, we use cookies to help provide an accurate count of votes on poll pages. We do
not and will not send spam emails to email addresses entered into youpoll.me. We hold a very strict no
spam policy. We do not sell, rent, share, trade, or give away any of your personally identifiable
information. We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are
set out in this privacy policy.

Do you have to give us this information to use the Service?
Of course not! You are not obligated to sign up for a user account to use the Service. You may also set
your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services, or to indicate when a
cookie is being set by us. However, it’s important to remember that many of our services will not be
available if your cookies are disabled.
What information can you share?
Youpoll.me lets users share information with others. Remember that when you share information publicly,
it may be indexable by search engines. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any
personally identifying information. Our services provide you with different options on sharing and
removing your content.
Can you access and delete your content?
Whenever you use our services, we aim to provide you with access to your content. If that information is
wrong, we strive to give you ways to delete it – unless we have to keep that information for legitimate
business or legal purposes. When deleting your content, we may ask you to verify your identity (sign into
your user account) before you can act on your request. We may reject requests that are unreasonably
repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, risk the privacy of others, or would be extremely
impractical.
What information do we share?
We do not share your email address with companies, organizations and individuals outside of Creative
Pages LLC unless one of the following circumstances applies:
     With your consent
      We may share your email address with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Creative
      Pages LLC when we have your consent to do so.
     For legal reasons
      We will share your email address with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Creative
      Pages LLC if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the
      information is reasonably necessary to:
       o Meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
       o Enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.
       o Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
       o Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Creative Pages LLC, our users or
            the public as required or permitted by law.
If Creative Pages LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we reserve the right to
transfer information about you to the successor-in-interest. In any of these events, Creative Pages
LLC will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different
privacy policy.
How is your information protected?
We work hard to protect youpoll.me and our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized
alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. All user accounts are password-protected and
encrypted using SSL. However, please note that we do not guarantee account security. Hardware or
software failure, unauthorized use and other factors may lead to a security breach.
What does this privacy policy apply to?
Our privacy policy applies to all of the services offered on youpoll.me, but excludes services that have
separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this privacy policy.
Can this privacy policy change?
Our privacy policy may change from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page
and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.
